How is it?
How was my acting just now?
Did I fool you?
Did anyone cry because of me?
Come on, let me see.
Let me see.
Not a single one.
Coach, you lied to us.
It seems so.
I almost cried.
Just kidding.
To liven things up.
Don't worry.
The school has allowed me to stay.
Really?
Alright.
Enough playing.
Let's get down to business.
The school
has allowed us to continue
to continue in the competition.
Guo Rui
has been disciplined by Yudong.
Then we must give it our all.
Do you have confidence?
Yes!
Good!
Saturday's match against Yudong.
Yudong is indeed strong,
but on the field,
there are always stories
of the underdog winning.
What's more,
we have a secret weapon.
Hurry up, guys.
Hurry up.
Chen Song.
Hello, we meet again.
I heard you transferred to our class.
We're classmates from now on.
Really?
Then we'll go to class together,
and play basketball together.
Coach Su asked me to take you there.
They are all waiting for you.
Let's go.
OK.
This is the secret weapon I mentioned.
Xie Yizhou
will join our basketball club
from now on.
Why are you here?
Don't you have to
prepare for the game?
What are you up to?
That's so mean.
I've decided to
transfer to Yibei.
Did you get kicked out
for helping us clear our names
with your account?
Yeah.
You got expelled?
That's so sad!
We're so sorry!
Just kidding.
I'd already decided
to transfer here.
It was a plan within a plan.
Black-hearted Tangyuan,
you haven't changed a bit.
Alright,
from now on,
we're family.
You know them,
so I won't introduce.
Come on.
Welcome.
Where's Fu Binyan?
Dr. Qin said
there's an innovative therapy
in the capital.
Let's go check it out.
Okay.
But can I
hold on until the quarterfinals?
This match is very important.
I want to be there.
Come on.
Let's take a picture together.
Three, two, one.
Good.
Your skills have improved.
Yeah.
I know you've improved.
Look how handsome you are!
Where did you go?
I went to the classroom to grab something.
Where's Coach Su?
He said he had family matters to attend to,
so he went home.
It seems
he can't keep up the act anymore.
What do you mean
by that?
Coach Su lied to us.
He's finished his internship
and is about to leave Yibei.
But he agreed with the school
to keep coaching us
until the next game
to avoid disrupting the team.
What?
Why is this happening?
The school is just following the rules.
There's nothing we can do.
Is there really no other way
to turn this around?
But I have an idea.
Maybe it can help Coach Su
get back on his feet.
Here we go,
the moment I've been
looking forward to!
You're exaggerating.
[Zhou Yang,]
[do you remember]
[the student file]
[we looked through?]
Of course.
I've found
the person you're looking for.
Really?
Can you two
stop encrypting your calls?
Everyone,
listen to me.
We don't have
much time left.
Coach.
Hello, Coach.
Why did you
call me over on the weekend?
And why is it such a big deal?
Coach,
we know you're leaving.
Coach
We will definitely practice hard.
But
coach
we have a gift for you.
Gift?
What gift?
Show yourself.
Long time no see.
Captain Sun
We are all acquaintances.
What brings you here?
Ask him.
We found
their contact information
in the files
and split up
to find them.
I didn't know you were
part of the basketball club.
That's all history.
When the kids said you were leaving,
I disagreed.
You can't leave the school
without my permission.
When I heard about the club,
I came here right away.
I'll be off soon.
Captain,
we haven't seen each other for years.
Look at us now.
You
You've kept in good shape.
Always maintaining
the physique of an unmarried young man.
Right.
I never thought I'd come back here,
and stand on the same basketball court
with you all.
It's really great.
Coach, look at me.
Come on.
It's so memorable.
Look, the coach is about to cry.
One more.
He must be moved to tears.
That's great.
Coach,
your jersey.
Jersey?
What do you mean?
Of course, it's for playing basketball.
Today,
we're having
the showdown between the old and new basketball clubs.
Are you ready?
Yes!
Bring it on!
Come on!
Nice shot!
Wow!
The old team is so good!
Nice shot!
Captain,
this feeling is back.
If they keep playing like this,
our team
will be outplayed.
No way.
Trust them.
Nice pass.
Don't underestimate them.
Captain,
we'll go.
Nice!
Everyone must be tired, right?
Not at all!
We're good!
No problem, Captain!
Okay.
Let's go.
Go!
Catch the ball!
Most Valuable Player!
It's been a long time
since I played like this.
Let's celebrate.
Come on.
Cheers.
Coach,
actually, we
contacted Changxia,
but he
has settled in another city,
so he couldn't make it.
He asked us
to say sorry to you
on his behalf.
It's all in the past.
I'm very happy that you can
invite them here today.
Really.
As long as you invite us,
we can come anytime.
Right.
Go through the north gate.
I'm familiar with the north gate.
Thank you all.
I really like your gift.
Next,
let's take
the momentum from the seniors
to face Yudong.
Do you have confidence?
Yes!
Yibei Basketball Club,
go, go, go!
It was here
that I watched you play.
Who knew we'd
actually be teammates now?
Isn't this
just like a dream come true?
You've been better than me for a while.
I've always wanted to ask you,
why did you decide to transfer to Yibei?
I play basketball to have fun.
But at the Middle School Affiliated to the Institute of Physical Education,
everyone just wants to win.
There's no joy in it.
Until I met you again
and saw everyone at Yibei,
I finally realized
this is how I want to play basketball.
Do you really
just play for fun?
Don't you care about winning or losing?
It's not that I don't care.
Winning is definitely enjoyable.
But
losing with my favorite partners
doesn't seem so bad.
Am I too lacking in ambition?
Not at all.
This is quite good.
Only by relaxing your mindset
can you better enjoy the game.
What about you?
You must want to win the next game, right?
If it were in the past,
I would definitely tell you
to win,
you must win.
Winning is meaningful,
and losing means failure.
What about now?
Now,
the result doesn't seem to be
the standard for everything anymore.
During this period,
our team
has been through so much together.
We almost couldn't compete,
and even faced disbandment.
But in the end, we returned
to the competition.
For us,
we have already won.
So winning or losing doesn't matter.
It does matter.
But no matter the outcome,
it can't stop us
from moving forward.
So,
I won't be afraid anymore.
Then I'll be with you
no matter the outcome.
Okay.
Good luck.
Secret weapon, Xie Yizhou.
Fighting!
My idol and captain,
Gu Chenyang.
Senior Zhou Yang,
do you remember
that you promised me to join the Basketball Club
right here?
Of course.
I just didn't expect
so many things would happen.
Do you think
there are more good things
or bad things?
As long as we
experience it together,
it will become a good thing.
By the way,
I have something for you.
This is the badge of our basketball team.
I specially ordered it for everyone.
So cool!
I'm sure everyone will like it.
I hope wearing it
will make our team
stronger.
Well,
I'll give you a gift too.
My favorite milk candies.
Have some.
Thanks.
When
will I
be as thoughtful
as you?
Unlike me,
who only knows to put candy in my pocket.
Still thinking about being a brother?
I think
you don't have to be like me.
Having a brother
who can always produce candy
is also cool.
Really?
Although you don't always
think things through,
your optimism
is something no one can match.
You're always so cheerful,
just like this candy,
bringing us all
a constant stream of small joys.
So,
just be yourself.
Be yourself.
Lin Qingyuan,
be yourself.
Be a happy self.
And be a
super nice brother.
Zhou Yang,
be a better self.
Be happy with mom forever.
[You shouted here alone last time.]
[This time, I'm with you.]
[The game is about to start.]
[Yibei Basketball Club,]
[go for it!]
Brother Yu,
the dishes are all here.
Order more if you want.
Thank you.
Chen Xiaosong,
you're still growing.
Eat more.
Try this.
Help yourself.
It's on me.
What are you thinking about?
You've been
looking preoccupied lately.
I've noticed
I'm getting
more into basketball.
Isn't that a good thing?
I used to think
my favorite thing was writing.
Now, I play basketball more,
write less,
and have less inspiration.
Do you think
this is a punishment for betraying
my dreams?
You're overthinking.
Life is long.
If you only do one thing,
wouldn't you feel bored?
Don't forget
my dream is
to make the Pulsar Band
famous all over the world.
But that doesn't stop me from playing basketball.
But what if
they conflict one day?
If they conflict,
it depends on which one is more important
which is more important.
For me now,
the competition is definitely more important.
And you?
Competition is important.
Hello, Brother Xu.
[Haoyu,]
[good news.]
[There's a New Star Music Project,]
[a nationwide student band]
[battle.]
I showed them
your video.
They want to invite you.
Really?
When is it?
This Saturday.
Do you have time?
This Saturday?
We have a competition.
I probably can't make it.
Oh, I see.
It's a rare opportunity.
Think about it again.
Give me an answer when you decide.
Okay.
Thank you, Xu.
Bye.
Peng Pai
Then you won't go.
I just said
the competition is definitely the most important thing
for me now.
But that doesn't mean
I gave up the band.
So you're the same.
Hello.
Your iced water.
Thank you.
I told you
there was something wrong with your thermos.
Why are you here?
I'm worried about you.
So,
you're keeping ice water
in your thermos?
Why?
Is it because of your heart?
Is it serious?
Was it triggered by something
online recently?
Whether it's serious or not,
the doctor will know best.
Then you should go see a doctor quickly.
I will.
But
I have to wait until the next competition is over.
It's okay.
This is for ice compress.
So,
you use ice water compress every day
for us?
For myself, too.
I don't want to miss
such a critical battle.
What's that look?
I'm fine.
Congrats.
You're the first to notice.
Should I keep it a secret for you?
No need.
Telling or hiding it
will just make them worry.
Let it be.
The basketball club really can't do without you.
Even if you don't play,
you're still
our rock.
Gu Chenyang and Zhou Yang
feel more at ease
when they see you.
Your heart condition is indeed bad,
but it's also because of you
that everyone feels at ease.
You're making it sound
like you're mourning me.
What are you talking about?
Say "pish pish pish".
Say it.
Pish pish pish.
That's enough.
You've been
smiling more and more lately.
Fu Binyan,
I'll be on the sidelines
for the next game.
If you feel unwell,
just call me.
I'll be there right away.
Don't worry.
I'm here for you.
Okay.